(Amy:)Sheldon, what...
what are you doing?
(Sheldon:)Just being
the un-socialized eccentric
(Sheldon:)my mother
always thought I was.
(Mary:)You startin' to see
why I didn't go in there?
(Mary:)Sheldon, if you're trying
to prove me wrong,
(Mary:)the tighty-whities on your head
ain't changing my mind.
(Amy:)We're ignoring
the fins... Okay.
(Sheldon:)Yeah. And I don't understand
why you're taking her side.
(Sheldon:)By being my girlfriend, she's
saying you're a weirdo, too.
(Amy:)I don't think that's
what she's saying.
(Sheldon:)And...?
(Amy:)That's exactly
what she was saying.
(Sheldon:)Can you believe my mother
thinks we're both strange?
Absolutely not!
(Penny:)That's... too loud.
(Leonard:)Absolutely not.
(Amy:)Well, after that,
Sheldon and I
(Amy:)got out of the
house for a while.
(Sheldon:)Well, first we buttered my feet
to get the swim fins off,
(Sheldon:)and then we went out.